Trice, Harrison M. Additional Papers /4164
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Michigan State Occupational Alcohol Consultation Program - Grant Application, 1977 (Box 46.1, Folder 3)
- Michigan State University Alcohol Project - Grant Application, 1978 (Box 46.1, Folder 4)
- NYU Medical Center Research Group - Grant Application, 1984 (Box 46.1, Folder 5)
- University of Arkansas Grant Review - HMT, 1978 (Box 46.1, Folder 6)
- University of Michigan, "ADM Disorders" study - Grant Information, 1984 (Box 46.1, Folder 7)
- University of Michigan EAP Follow-up Strategy - Grant Application, 1984 (Box 46.1, Folder 8)
- University of Missouri EAP - HMT Review, 1978 (Box 46.1, Folder 9)
- University of South Carolina (Financing of Alcoholism Treatment) - Grant Application, 1979 (Box 46.1, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Akron Area EAP Grant Application, 1979 (Box 46.1, Folder 11)
- IUE District #2 EAP Grant Application and HMT Review, 1979 (Box 46.1, Folder 12)
- Cleveland Area Teamster EAP - Grant Application, 1978 (Box 46.1, Folder 13)
- United Autoworkers Occupational Alcohol Services Grant Renewal - Application and Review, 1980 (Box 46.1, Folder 14)
- United Autoworkers Alcohol Services Outline (Box 46.1, Folder 15)
- UAW Renewal Grant Application, 1979 (Box 46.1, Folder 16)
- St. Louis UAW "Troubled Employee Recovery Program" - Grant Application, 1976 (Box 46.1, Folder 17)
- International Longshoremen's Association - HMT Review, 1978 (Box 46.1, Folder 18)
- Correspondence and Articles Regarding Alcoholism in California Bar Association, 1975-1978 (Box 46.1, Folder 19)
- Report: Occupational Program for Michigan Legal Profession (Box 46.1, Folder 20)
- Department of Human Services Publications Regarding Research Guidelines, 1983 (Box 46.1, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1984 (Box 46.1, Folder 22)
- Occupational Alcoholism Publications (Box 46.1, Folder 23)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 422-30-01-4 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 422-30-05-9 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 431-31-01-3 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 431-31-04-7 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 431-32-01-5 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 432-33-01-5 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 432-33-09-16 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 432-33-18-22 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 432-33-23-28 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 432-34-01-4 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 432-34-05-8 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 432-34-09-11 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 432-34-12-15 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 511-35-01-4 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 511-35-05-8 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 512-36-02-6 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 512-36-07-10, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 512-37-01-4 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 512-37-05-8 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 512-38-01-3 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 512-38-04-7 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 531-39-01-5 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 532-40-01-5 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 532-40-06-10 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 611-41-01-4 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 621-42-01-6 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 622-43-01-6 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 631-44-01-5 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 632-45-01-4 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 632-45-05-9 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 712-46-01-4 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 712-46-05-7 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interview 711-47-01 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 711-47-02-4 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 712-48-01-3 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 712-48-04-6 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 721-49-01-4 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 721-49-05-7 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 722-50-01-3 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 722-50-04-6 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 732-51-01-4 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 732-51-05-7 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 732-51-08-11 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 732-51-12-15 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 732-51-16-18 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 732-51-19-23 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 732-51-24-27 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 811-53-01-4 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 812-54-01-6 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 812-54-07-9 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 812-54-10-14 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 812-54-15-18 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 812-54-19-23 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 822-55-01-5 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 822-55-05-10 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 822-55-11-16 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 831-56-01-5 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 911-58-01-2 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 911-58-03-4 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 911-59-01-3 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interview 911-59-04 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 912-60-01-5 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 912-60-06-10 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 912-60-11-15 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 912-60-16-20 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 912-60-21-24 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 912-60-25-28 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 912-61-01-3 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 912-61-04-6 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 921-62-01-3 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 921-62-04-6 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 921-63-01-5 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 922-64-01-5 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 922-64-06-10 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 922-64-11-15 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 922-64-16-20 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 922-65-01-4 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 922-65-05-9 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-66-01-5 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-66-06-10 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- F.F. File Buildings Codesheets - All Files (Box 52.1, Folder 1)
- Data Modification Codesheets (Box 52.1, Folder 2)
- Interpretive Coding File Building Codesheets - For Alcoholism Coordinator, EEO Coordinator, Director, and Supervisor (Box 52.1, Folder 3)
- Error Checks (Box 52.1, Folder 4)
- 10 EEO P.I.S. Codesheets (Box 52.1, Folder 5)
- Interpretive Coding - Codesheets for Alcoholism, EEO, Director, Supervisor (Box 52.1, Folder 6)
- EEO Codesheets punched (Box 52.1, Folder 7)
- Trice - Supervisor Regular Coding (Box 52.1, Folder 8)
- Codesheets for Miscellaneous Runs - Summer '75, 1975 (Box 52.1, Folder 9)
- Correction Made on Super File (Box 52.1, Folder 10)
- Trice - Director Codesheets (Box 52.1, Folder 11)
- Trice - Alcohol Coordinator Regular Coding (Box 52.1, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-66-11-15 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-66-16-20 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-66-21-27 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-66-28-30 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-67-01-4 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-67-05-8 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-68-01-6 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-68-07-13 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-69-01-4 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-69-05-9 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-69-09-16 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-70-01-5 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 932-70-06-8 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 111-71-01-3, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 111-71-04-5, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 411-72-01-7, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 911-73-01-5, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Personnel Information Summary #1 - Plum Island Animal Disease Center, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Personnel Information Summary #2 Agriculture Soil Conservation Service State Office (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Personnel Information Summary #4 United States Forest Service (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Personnel Information Summary #5 USDA Agricultural Research Service (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Personnel Information Service #6 USDA Forest Service Department Bureau Division Branch (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Personnel Information Service #7 Middle Atlantic Coastal Fisheries Center (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Personnel Information Service #8 Census Bureau (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Personnel Information Service #9 United States Census Bureau (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Personnel Information Service #10 General Services Administration Federal Supply Schedules (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Personnel Information Service #11 GSA FSS (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Personnel Information Service #12 General Services Administration Public Buildings Service - Binghamton Group (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Personnel Information Service #13 Fire and Security - Maintenance and Operations - Custodial (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Personnel Information Service #14 General Services Administration Buildings Management Division (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Personnel Information Service #15 GSA Supply Distribution Facility Belle Mead (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Personnel Information Service #16 GSA Public Buildings Service - Newark Field Office (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Personnel Information Service #17 GSA Office of Civil Rights Region I (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Personnel Information Service #18 General Services Administration (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Personnel Information Service #19 GSA Public Buildings Service Baltimore Area, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Personnel Information Service #20 GSA Public Buildings Service Philadelphia Area (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Personnel Information Service #21 Untitled (Box 54, Folder 27)
- Personnel Information Service #22 Social Security Administration San Juan Office, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 28)
- Personnel Information Service #23 SSA Newark Office (Box 54, Folder 29)
- Personnel Information Service #24 SSA Buffalo Office (Box 54, Folder 30)
- Personnel Information Service #25 Department of Health, Education, and Welfare - Various Facilities (Box 54, Folder 31)
- Personnel Information Service #26 Department of Health, Education, and Welfare - New York Branch (Box 54, Folder 32)
- Personnel Information Service #27 Food and Drug Administration (Box 54, Folder 33)
- Personnel Information Service #28 Department of Health, Education, and Welfare Social Rehabilitation Services (Box 54, Folder 34)
- Personnel Information Service #29 FDA Various Facilities (Box 54, Folder 35)
- Personnel Information Service #30 Department of Health, Education, and Welfare Boston Office (Box 54, Folder 36)
- Personnel Information Service #31 FDA Consumer Safety Division (Box 54, Folder 37)
- Personnel Information Service #32 SSA District Office (Box 54, Folder 38)
- Personnel Information Service #33 Department of Health, Education, and Welfare Region III (Box 54, Folder 39)
- Personnel Information Service #34 United States Public Health Service Hospital Norfolk, Virginia (Box 54, Folder 40)
- Personnel Information Service #36 Department of Housing and Urban Development Various Branches (Box 54, Folder 41)
- Personnel Information Service #37 Untitled (Box 54, Folder 42)
- Personnel Information Service #38 Untitled (Box 54, Folder 43)
- Personnel Information Service #39 HUD, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 44)
- Personnel Information Service #40 HUD Pittsburgh Area Office (Box 54, Folder 45)
- Personnel Information Service #41 Geological Survey, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 46)
- Personnel Information Service #42 National Park Service Boston Region, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 47)
- Personnel Information Service #43 Bureau of Sport Fisheries and Wildlife (Box 54, Folder 48)
- Personnel Information Service #44 Department of the Interior - Geological Survey Bureau - Water Resources District Office (Box 54, Folder 49)
- Personnel Information Service #45 Department of Interior Division and Branch (Box 54, Folder 50)
- Personnel Information Service #46 Department of the Interior San Juan District (Box 54, Folder 51)
- Personnel Information Service #47 Immigration and Naturalization Service - Various Branches (Box 54, Folder 52)
- Personnel Information Service #48 Department of Justice - Immigration and Naturalization Service (Box 54, Folder 53)
- Personnel Information Service #49 Office of Operations (Box 54, Folder 54)
- Personnel Information Service #50 District Office (Box 54, Folder 55)
- Personnel Information Service #51 Immigration and Naturalization Service - Deportation, Citizenship, and Travel Control Branches, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 56)
- Personnel Information Service #53 Midtown, New York District Office (Box 54, Folder 57)
- Personnel Information Service #54 Federal Aviation Administration New York Air Traffic Control Center (Box 54, Folder 58)
- Personnel Information Service #55 FAA New England Region (Box 54, Folder 59)
- Personnel Information Service #56 FAA Pennsylvania Area (Box 54, Folder 60)
- Personnel Information Service #58 IRS Field Office, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 61)
- Personnel Information Service #59 IRS Field Branch III (Box 54, Folder 62)
- Personnel Information Service #60 IRS Newark District, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 63)
- Personnel Information Service #61 IRS Brooklyn Field Office (Box 54, Folder 64)
- Personnel Information Service #62 Department of the Treasury Internal Revenue Service (Box 54, Folder 65)
- Personnel Information Service #63 IRS Audit Division (Box 54, Folder 66)
- Personnel Information Service #64 IRS Hartford Office (Box 54, Folder 67)
- Personnel Information Service #65 IRS District Office, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 68)
- Personnel Information Service #66 IRS Philadelphia District Office, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 69)
- Personnel Information Service #67 IRS (Box 54, Folder 70)
- Personnel Information Service #68 IRS National Computer Center (Box 54, Folder 71)
- Personnel Information Service #69 IRS (Box 54, Folder 72)
- Personnel Information Service #70 IRS Parkersburg District (Box 54, Folder 73)
- Personnel Information Service #71 USDA State Conservation Service, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 74)
- Personnel Information Service #72 FDA - Office of the Deputy Regional Food and Drug Director (Box 54, Folder 75)
- Personnel Information Service #73 IRS - Collection and Taxpayer Service Division (Box 54, Folder 76)
- Personnel Information Service #99 Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 77)
- Personnel Information Service Miscellaneous Information (Box 54, Folder 78)
- Evaluation of New York State Occupational Alcoholism Consultation - Project Description, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Director Codebook for Fixed Format Items (Box 54.1, Folder 1)
- Monthly Contact and Demographic Codebook (Box 54.1, Folder 2)
- Supervisor Fixed Format Codebook (Box 54.1, Folder 3)
- Data Modification Reports, 1975 (Box 54.1, Folder 4)
- Monthly Organization Contact and Demographic Codebook (Box 54.1, Folder 5)
- Training Codebook (Box 54.1, Folder 6)
- Monthly Activities Codebook (Box 54.1, Folder 7)
- Alcoholism Coordinator Fixed Format Codebook (Box 54.1, Folder 8)
- Structure and Environment Variables Codebook, 1974 (Box 54.1, Folder 9)
- "B Manager" Codebook (Box 54.1, Folder 10)
- Interpretive Codebooks and HMT Notes (Box 54.1, Folder 11)
- Face Sheet and Ethnicity Codes (Box 54.1, Folder 12)
- Cumulative Codebook Changes, 1976 (Box 54.1, Folder 13)
- Printouts of Updates - Backup Tapes, 1975 (Box 54.1, Folder 14)
  Computer printouts
- Printouts of Copying Tapes, 1975 (Box 54.1, Folder 15)
- Printouts of Copy Tapes, 1975 (Box 54.1, Folder 16)
- Variable List Updates, 1975 (Box 54.1, Folder 17)
- Alcoholism Coordinator Fixed Format Codebook (Box 54.1, Folder 18)
- Supervisor Codebook (Box 54.1, Folder 19)
- Write-Ins for Interpretive Coding (Box 54.1, Folder 20)
- EEO Codebook (Box 54.1, Folder 21)
- Functionary and Director Correction Codes, 1975 (Box 54.1, Folder 22)
- Inventory of Alcohol Data, 1974 (Box 54.1, Folder 23)
- IBM Keypunch Operating Instructions, 1972-1975 (Box 54.1, Folder 24)
- Computer Tape Numbers (Box 54.1, Folder 25)
- Computer Tape Notes (Box 54.1, Folder 26)
- Computer Accounts, 1975 (Box 54.1, Folder 27)
  Includes computer punch cards
- Index of Computer Printout Analyses, 1977 (Box 54.1, Folder 28)
- Basic Statistics Summarized in Codebooks Part 1 (Box 54.1, Folder 29)
- Basic Statistics Summarized in Codebooks Part 2 (Box 54.1, Folder 30)
- Blocked Off Coding Forms (Box 54.1, Folder 31)
  Includes computer printouts and punch cards
- Project Grant Applications, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Memo from Trice regarding outcome evaluation strategies, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Preliminary Findings - Descriptive Phase Working Papers, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Second Year Findings - Working Papers November 1976 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Rival Hypothesis (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Project Contact Lists, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Evaluation of New York State Occupational Alcohol Consultation - Budget Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Pre-Grant Correspondence, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Contract between Cornell and New York State Department of Mental Hygiene, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Grant Renewal Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- First Year Correspondence with New York State Department of Mental Hygiene, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Second Year Grant Renewal Notes and Application, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Third Year Grant renewal Notes and Application, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Draft Organizational Contract Form Correspondence, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Participation Invite Correspondence, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Organizational Pretest Inventory (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Project Form Letters - Regional and County Offices, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Organization Sample Set (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Sample Participating Agencies Lists - by categories (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Standard Shade Roller Employee Assistance Program Overview, 1974-1977 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Notes - Occupational Alcoholism Program Union Participants, 1975-1977 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Organization Coding Lists - alphabetical (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Organization Coding Lists - notes (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Corporate Headquarters Alcoholism Project Data Analysis/Evaluation, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Occupational Alcoholism Programs - Grant Applications, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 26)
- Occupational Alcoholism Programs - Grant Applications continued, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 27)
- Occupational Alcoholism Programs - Grant Applications and Draft Proposals, 1974-1977 (Box 55, Folder 28)
- NYS Regional Occupational Alcoholism Program Grant Approval, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 29)
- NYS Occupational Alcoholism Program Proposals, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 30)
- NYS Plan for Developing an Alcohol Abuse Program, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 31)
- Nine Month Action Plan Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 55, Folder 32)
- Regional Associate Alcoholism Program Representative - Job Description (Box 55, Folder 33)
- Guidelines for Local Occupational Alcoholism Consultation Services, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 34)
- Summary of Occupational Program Consultant Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 55, Folder 35)
- NYS Regional Occupational Alcoholism Program Organization Charts, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 36)